Why did you only choose students
within this school for your works of art?
なぜ 同じ学園内の生徒ばかりを素材に選んだのかな
This academy is a
girls' boarding school.
全寮制女子学校というこの学園の教育方針を 槙島先生はどうお考えですか
What do you think of their
education policy, Mr. Makishima?
We were so close.
あと一歩でしたね
Rikako Ouryou has already
been put on the wanted list.
王陵璃華子はすでに指名手配されています
It's just a matter of time.
時間の問題です
She'll disappear.
消えるな
What?
Come with me. I wanna talk to you.
ちょっと来い 話がある
What is it? If you have a
problem with me, just spit it out.
何だよ
文句があるならはっきり言え
I'm sorry.
すまなかった
It was me who got emotional.
He wasn't your delusion.
感情的になっていたのは俺の方だった
やつはお前の妄想じゃなかった
Don't worry about it.
気にするな
If you took everything Enforcers
say seriously, you'd be a poor Inspector.
執行官の言うことを全て真に受けてたら 監視官は務まらない
That's how it is, right?
そういうもんだろ
But...
だが…
It feels like my prey's tail just
brushed the tip of my nose.
獲物の尻尾が鼻先をかすめたみたいな感じだ
For the first time in a long while,
I'm feeling pretty good now, Gino.
俺は今 久しぶりにとてもいい気分だよ　ギノ
My head is overflowing with thoughts
I can't allow anyone to know about
誰にも見せられないもの
脑海里充斥着的喧嚣
頭の中溢れて
谁都无法看见
I've strayed into a world void of even mistakes
間違いさえも無い世界へ
我在这个不会犯错的机械世界里
迷い込んでる
一路行走一路彷徨
It's being rubbed in so deep it's hard to believe
あり得ないほど擦り込まれてる
与你擦肩而过的次数多到近乎异常
This "world" that holds
only what the eye can see
目に見えるものだけの“世界”現象
我眼里能看到的 就是我全部的世界
Can I flush out the truth?
暴きだせるかな
能否打破它
Plastic Tac Tic,
no one can go crazy anymore
Plastic Tac Tic
plastic tac tic
もう誰もおかしくなれないよ
所有人都习以为常
You, too, are in a plastic beautiful world
貴様もplastic beautiful world
你也一样 plastic beautiful world
In a world with too much beauty,
for some reason I can't see the light
美しすぎる世界に
在这个过于完美的世界里
僕はなぜか
我为什么
光が見えなくて
看不到光明的方向
My bursting heart is an eternal reflection
破裂していく心が
心在一步步碎裂
無限のリフレクション
回音无限
secret remains for you
为你留下这个秘密
Secret remains for you
Don't expose these false colors and futures
見せかけの色と
徒有其表的鲜艳色彩及未来
未来を暴かないで
别打破它
fake's plastic world
keep it secret motion
就让这个秘密继续秘密下去
本字幕由诸神字幕组制作 更多字幕欢迎访问http://www.kamigami.org
翻译:草泥马 TMR@10 校对:西西   后期:时末
#09 Paradise Fruit
Okay.
よし
Have you decided?
お決まりですか
Yep.
うん　この組み合わせでお気に入りに登録しておいて
Put this outfit combination
in my "favorites."
Roger!
了解です
Oh! Do you have a date?
もしかしてデートとか
I-It's not like that!
ちっ　違うよ
Holo team! Use the pattern
that we discussed yesterday!
ホロ班　昨日の打ち合わせどおりのパターンで
Provided by the Cyberization Health
Bureau, Ministry of Welfare
Advanced Medical Treatments of the
Future that Will Change Your Life
Okay!
はい
Hmm... I'm not sure...
うーん　どうかな
Isn't it a little too flashy?
People might feel it's tacky instead.
ちょっと派手過ぎて 逆に安くねえかな
Well then, we'll try
some other patterns, too.
じゃあ　違うパターンちょっと試してみますね
How about getting
a present for your date?
デートのお相手にご贈答品はいかがですか
Also, I could coordinate a bouquet...
あとは花束のコーディネートも
I said it's not like that, didn't I?!
違うって言ってるでしょ キャンセル　メモリー削除
Cancel! Delete memory!
As you wish.
Speculation circuit will be reset!
かしこまりました 推測回路　リセットしま～す
Candy, turn on some news.
キャンディ　何かニュース
The Ministry of Welfare
uploaded a recommended video.
厚生省からお薦めの動画がアップされています
Then play that one.
じゃあそれで
Today, we have Mr. Toyohisa Senguji,
a pioneer of whole-body cyberization
本日は全身サイボーグ化のパイオニア
and the Chairman of the Teito
Network Construction Corporation,
地下再開発を進める帝都ネットワーク建設の会長
a company that works on
underground redevelopment.
泉宮寺豊久さんにお越しいただきました
Chairman of Teito Network Construction Corporation               Toyohisa Senguji
Thanks for having me.
よろしくお願いします
The use of cyborg technology for
medical purposes is now commonplace.
医療目的のサイボーグ技術は私たちの生活にすっかりなじんだものとなりました
However, it's still rare to see
someone like Chairman Senguji,
しかし 泉宮寺会長のように脳と神経系以外全てをサイボーグ化した例は
who, except for his brain and
nervous system, is entirely cyborg.
まだまだ珍しいものです
It's a mystery to me
不思議なんですよ
why other people haven't
given up their limiting bodies.
なぜ みんな早く不自由な肉体を捨ててしまわないのか
Limiting, you say?
不自由…ですか
Plato said that our souls
were imprisoned in our bodies.
肉体は魂の牢獄だとプラトンは言いました
You seem to be in a bad
mood already, Mr. Kogami.
いきなり不機嫌そうですね 狡噛さん
When I tried to smoke,
that thing tried to bite me.
たばこ吸おうとしたら そいつにかみつかれそうになったんだよ
What's your problem?!
んだ　こら
What was that about? Geez...
いきなり何なんですか　もう
Sorry.
悪いな
Hm?
Well, please don't worry
about it. I'm curious, too, so...
いえ　気にしないでください
私も　興味があるので
I'm finding new pleasures
in my life all the time.
私の人生はますます楽しみを増している
I never expected that overcoming
aging would lead to such happiness.
老いを克服することがこれほどまでに幸福なこととは
Unless you embrace a cyberized body,
you won't understand it.
機械の体を受け入れないかぎり 理解はできないでしょう
But even with the latest technology,
しかし 最新の技術をもってしても 脳の寿命は１５０年程度とされています
it is estimated that the
brain's lifespan is about 150 years.
I hear that we're still quite a ways
away from complete cyberization of the brain.
脳の完全な機械化はまだまだクリアできていない課題が山積みとか
If I tax my brain to its limits,
I can squeeze a bit more life out of it.
限界まで酷使すれば まだ私の脳には余裕がある
So I'm counting on them to
find a breakthrough in the meantime.
その間にブレークスルーが起きることを期待しますよ
I see. If that actually happens, then...
なるほど もしもそれが起きたとしたら
That's right. The era of
immortality will have arrived.
さよう　不死の時代の到来です
It's said that God created
man in his own image.
神は自分に似せて 人をつくったという
Isn't it about time for us humans
to be a little more like God?
そろそろ　もう少し 人が神に似てもいいのでは
What do you think about gaining
eternal youth and immortality
狡噛さんはどう思います
サイボーグ化の不老不死って
by becoming a cyborg?
I'm not interested.
興味ないな
Life as a latent criminal isn't the
sort of thing you'd want to go on forever.
潜在犯の人生は末永く続けたくなるようなもんじゃない
But... if the social system
is more developed one day,
でも　いつかもっと社会制度が発達すれば
the rights of latent criminals may improve.
潜在犯の権利だって改善されるかも
No wonder your Psycho-Pass
tends to stay so clear.
あんたのサイコパス 濁りにくいわけだ
According to a survey,
アンケート調査によると 全身の５割を超えるサイボーグ化には
it seems that a majority
of people have answered
that they feel reluctant to
be more than 50% cyborg.
抵抗を感じると答えた方が大多数のようですが…
I do understand the
reluctance that those people feel.
抵抗があるという人の気持ちは分かりますよ
In the end, it's a matter of degree.
結局は程度の問題なんですよ
For example, you...
例えばあなた
You're quite the cyborg, too.
あなたも立派なサイボーグですよ
But I don't use artificial arms,
artificial legs, or artificial organs.
しかし　私は義手も義足も人工臓器も使っていません
But you do have some form of
portable information terminal, right?
何らかの携帯情報端末を持っていますよね
Well, yes... but doesn't everyone?
それはまあ 誰でも持っているのでは
A costume device, too?
コス·デバイスも
Of course.
もちろん
And, at home, you probably have
home automation and an AI secretary.
そして　家にはホームオートメーションとＡＩセクレタリー
Yes.
ええ
What would happen to you if all
the data in those devices was lost
それらのデータが災害や事故によって一気に失われたら
due to a disaster or accident?
あなたはどうなりますか
Well...
それは…
I wouldn't be able to do
any work until it gets restored.
復旧するまで何の仕事もできません
When you entrust so much of your
everyday life to those electronic devices,
自分の生活をそこまで電子的な装置に委託しているのに
the argument that you aren't
a cyborg isn't very convincing.
サイボーグではないと言っても説得力はありませんよ
To you, those portable terminals
are already your second brain.
あなたにとって携帯端末はすでに第二の脳だ
Isn't that right?
違いますか
It can be said that the history of science is
科学の歴史は人間の身体機能の拡張
a history of the expansion of
the human body's functionality,
つまり　人間機械化の歴史と言い換えても差し支えない
in other words,
the history of man's cyberization.
That's why it's a matter of degree.
だから　程度の問題なんです
Private Property
No Trespassing
Yes?
はい
Hello. It's me, Kogami.
どうも　狡噛です
Oh, hold on a sec.
ああ　ちょっと待って
I don't see much environment
Holo being used here.
環境ホロをほとんど使ってませんね
He doesn't like that kind of stuff.
そういうのが嫌いな人なんだ
It's been a while, Professor Saiga.
お久しぶりです　雑賀教授
Stop calling me professor. How many
years do you think it's been since I quit?
教授はよしてくれよ
辞めて何年たつと思ってるんだ
So that young lady is...
そっちのお嬢さんが…
I'm Akane Tsunemori, an Inspector
at the MWPSB. Nice to meet you.
初めまして 公安局の監視官 常守朱です
Thank you for seeing me today.
今日は　よろしくお願いします
Come in. I welcome you.
入りたまえ　歓迎するよ
Is coffee okay?
飲み物はコーヒーでいいかな
Yes.
ええ
Ah, yes.
あっ　はい
Well, coffee's all I've got, so...
といってもな コーヒー以外ないんだよ
Inspector Akane Tsunemori...
常守朱監視官
Yes?
はい
Are you from Chiba Prefecture?
千葉県出身かな
Yes, I am.
そうですけど
Your athletic ability isn't bad, and yet...
君は運動神経は悪くないのに 何でだろう
I wonder why...
Yeah...
そう…泳げない
...you can't swim.
What?!
Both of your parents are still alive.
両親はまだどちらもご存命
They're worried about their
only daughter not finding a boyfriend.
一人娘になかなか恋人ができないのを心配している
Uhm...
They were opposed to
you working at the MWPSB, too.
公安局入りにも反対だった
And, your grandfather or grandmother...
そして　祖父か祖母…
うん　祖母だな
It must be your grandmother.
She treated you with great affection.
かわいがってもらった かなりのおばあちゃん子だね
It seems that you
are quite the grandma's girl.
It's often true that the longer you spend
time with the elderly in your childhood,
幼児期 高齢者と長く過ごした人間ほど
成長してからホロアバターの人工知能と良好な関係を築くことが多い
the better the relationship
you can establish
with Holo Avatar AIs
in your adulthood.
You fit that pattern, Ms. Tsunemori.
そのパターンに常守さんも当てはまっている
Uhm...
あの…
You're as sharp as ever, Mr. Saiga.
相変わらずですね　雑賀先生
How... did you do that?
今の…どうやったんですか
Through simple observation.
ただ観察しただけさ
People manifest all sorts
of signs unconsciously.
人は無意識のうちに様々なサインを発している
Once you get the knack of it,
you can easily read those signs.
コツさえ覚えれば 簡単にそのサインを読み取れる
Mr. Jouji Saiga...
雑賀譲二先生
Your expertise is clinical psychology.
専門は臨床心理学
As I worked as a psychiatric examiner
and assisted in investigations and such,
精神鑑定や捜査協力なんかをしているうちに
my main focus shifted to
crime research before I knew it.
いつの間にか犯罪の研究に主軸が移ってしまったよ
I have two favors to ask you today.
今日は２つお願いがあります
Ask me anything.
何でも言ってくれ
First, I'd like you to give this
Inspector an intensive short course.
一つはこちらの監視官に短期集中講義を
Things like profiling...
プロファイリングとか時代遅れの方法ってことになってますけど
They say it's an outdated method,
but I'm very interested in it.
すごく興味があって
Or rather, I became interested recently.
ていうか　最近興味が出てきて
I'm a hermit. I actually feel grateful
for the opportunity to teach you.
こんな世捨て人に ありがたい話だよホントに
So, what's the other one?
で　もう一つは
I'd like to see the list of past course
attendees that you keep with you.
先生が保管している今までの受講生名簿を見せてください
Is that a request from the MWPSB?
それは公安局からの要請かな
No... it's a personal request.
いえ　個人的なお願いです
If it was an order,
I would've turned it down.
もしも命令だったとしたら断ったところだ
Who are you looking for?
誰を捜している？
I think this guy is the worst criminal
since the creation of the Sibyl System.
シビュラシステムの誕生以降 最悪の犯罪者だと思われます
What do you mean?
というと？
He's a high-level intellectual criminal
極めて高いレベルの知能犯
and is probably fit and in good health, too.
おそらく　肉体的にも頑健
He's someone with unique charisma.
特殊なカリスマ性を持ち
He rarely kills people with his own hands.
自分で直接手を下すことは少なく
He controls other people's
minds and influences them.
他人の精神を支配し影響を与え
Much like a music conductor,
he orchestrates one crime after another.
まるで音楽を指揮するように犯罪を重ねていく男です
Kogami, explain what charisma is.
狡噛
カリスマ性とは何だい？
I used it to mean
the nature of a hero or a ruler.
英雄的　支配者的資質という意味で使いましたが…
I'd give that answer... twenty points.
２０点…かな
Charisma has three elements.
カリスマ性には３つの要素がある
The nature of a hero or a prophet,
英雄的 預言者的資質　あるいは
an ability to simply make you
feel good when you're around them,
一緒にいて気持ちがいいというシンプルな空間演出能力
and the intelligence to eloquently
talk about all sorts of things.
そして　あらゆることを雄弁に語るための知性
Of those, which elements
does this guy you're looking for have?
狡噛が捜しているのはどのタイプかな
I think he has all of them.
全ての要素を備えていると考えられます
This is Yukimori Shibata,
an art teacher at Ousou Academy.
桜霜学園美術教師　柴田幸盛
Well, that's who he's supposed to be,
ということになっているが
but it turns out that he's actually
an old man in a nursing home
実際は介護施設に収容されたまったく無関係な老人だった
who has nothing to do with the academy.
His background profile was altered
彼の経歴が改ざんされ
and this guy used it when
he pretended to be a teacher.
教員に成り済ます上で利用されていた
It's malicious and clever of him
not to completely fake his background.
完全な偽造経歴じゃないところが
悪質かつ巧妙っすね
But to think that he worked as a teacher,
which put him in the public eye...
しかし　教師なんて人目に触れる仕事に就くとは
大胆なのか間抜けなのか
Is he daring or a fool?
Well, about that...
それがですね
...all the video data was destroyed.
映像データは全てクラッシュ
All we were able to
salvage was a short sound file.
辛うじて残っていたのはほんの短い音声ファイルのみ
There are only two methods left:
残された手段は昔ながらのモンタージュ写真と似顔絵作成の２つだけ
Creating a traditional photofit
picture and drawing a composite sketch.
Of course, we tried both methods.
もちろん どちらもやってみました
From the sound of it,
they didn't work?
その口ぶりからすると外れか
Right.
ええ
After all, the only lead we have is
the blurry picture Sasayama took, huh?
結局　佐々山が撮ったピンぼけの写真しか手掛かりはないってか
Did it help you at least a little?
少しはあんたの役に立ったか？
Y-Yes, it helped a lot!
はい　とても
He's an incredible teacher.
すごい先生です
I don't understand why his lectures
are not in the MWPSB's archive.
公安局のアーカイブに入ってないのが不思議でしかたありません
They wouldn't possibly put them in the archive.
アーカイブ化は無理だな
Did something happen?
何かあったんですか？
This was around the time that
シビュラシステムと大学制度が同時に存在していたころの話だ
both the Sibyl System and the
university system existed at the same time.
Mr. Saiga's special courses were
set up for the MWPSB's investigators.
公安局捜査官のために　雑賀先生の特別講義が設けられていた
But one day, a big problem came to light.
だがあるとき大問題が発覚した
The course attendees' Hues got clouded
and their Crime Coefficients rose.
受講生の色相が濁り 犯罪係数が上昇したんだ
Well, not everyone's did, though.
まっ全員じゃないがね
A one-on-one lecture like
the one you had today is okay.
今日のようなマンツーマンの講義なら大丈夫だ
Besides, it's hard to cloud your Hue.
それにあんたは色相が濁りにくいたちだしな
But...
でも…
...to think that just listening to
lectures raises your Crime Coefficient...
講義だけで犯罪係数が上がるなんて
Say there's a dark swamp
and you can't see the bottom.
底が見えない黒い沼がある
In order to check the swamp,
you have no choice but to jump in.
沼を調べるためには飛び込むしかない
Mr. Saiga is used to it since he's
dived in to investigate it so many times.
先生は何度も調査のために潜ったことがあって慣れている
But it's not like all his students can come
back safely after diving into the swamp.
でも全ての生徒が沼に潜って無事に戻ってこれるわけじゃない
There are gaps in their abilities
and simply their suitability, too.
能力差や単純に向き不向きもある
You seem like someone who'd dive
deep... and yet come back safely.
狡噛さんは深くまで潜りそうですね
それでもちゃんと帰ってくる
Well, I don't know about that.
いや　どうだかな
At least, the Sibyl System decided
that I couldn't come back.
少なくともシビュラシステムは
俺が帰ってこられなかったと判断した
Which animal do you think is most
cunning and does not risk extinction
最も狡猾で　いくら狩り殺しても絶滅の心配がない動物は何だと思う
no matter how many are hunted and killed?
That must be humans.
人間でしょ
I guess it was too easy, huh?
簡単過ぎたな
These days...
今はもう…
...they no longer issue hunting
licenses under normal circumstances.
普通の狩猟は許可が下りない
I really appreciate you, Makishima.
槙島君には感謝しているんだよ
That's not ivory... is it...
象牙…ではありませんね
I guess I haven't shown this to you before.
まだ見せたことはなかったな
Excluding the mouthpiece, this pipe
is made of Rikako Ouryou's bones.
このパイプはマウスピース以外は王陵璃華子の骨だよ
I see...
When I'm touching it like this...
こうして触っていると…
...my mind regains its youth.
心が若さを取り戻すんだよ
The souls of my terrified
prey give me energy.
恐怖に震え上がる獲物たちの魂が私に活力を与えてくれる
You've overcome your body's aging.
肉体の老いは克服した
All that's left is your mind?
あとは心 ですか？
Yeah, that's right.
そういうことだね
You maintain a healthy and sound life...
生命とは他の命を犠牲にすることで
...by sacrificing other lives.
健やかに保たれる
But if people only
seek youth for their bodies
だが　体の若さばかりを求め 心を養うすべを見失えば当然
and lose sight of the
means to cultivate their minds,
naturally, it will only lead to an
increase in the number of living dead.
生きながらに死んでいる亡者たちばかりが増えていく
How foolish, don't you think?
愚かしいかぎりではないか
The energy that comes from thrills...
スリルによる活力
It's a dangerous reward that goes
hand in hand with death, huh?
それは死と隣り合わせの危険な報酬ですな
That's right. In hunting,
the tougher your prey is,
そうとも
狩りの獲物は手ごわいほどにみずみずしい若さが手に入る
the fresher the youth you can gain from it.
With all that in mind,
そこまで仰せなら
I think I can arrange for your
next prey to be an exquisite one.
次は飛び切りの獲物をご用意できるかと
Oh?
It's an Enforcer from the MWPSB.
公安局執行官
MWPSB!
公安局
His name is...
名前は…
In the end, I guess checking
Professor Saiga's lecture attendees list
結局　雑賀教授の受講者名簿は空振りでしたね
didn't help much.
That's how it goes sometimes.
But if Makishima is a living man,
しかたがない
だがマキシマが生きている人間なら
he's left a trace somewhere for sure.
必ずどこかに足跡がある
I heard that you brought Inspector
Tsunemori to Jouji Saiga.
常守監視官を雑賀譲二に引き合わせたそうだな
Yeah.
ああ
That's because I asked him to.
それは　私が紹介を頼んで…
What're you doing? Are you trying
to drag her into your problem,
どういうつもりだ　彼女を巻き添えにしたいのか
making her a latent criminal who
strayed from the right path, like you?
貴様と同じ道を踏み外した潜在犯に
Wait a minute!
Are you treating me like a child?
ちょっと待ってください　私を子供扱いしてるんですか
As a matter of fact, you are a child!
事実として君は子供だ
A brat who's confused
about anything and everything!
右も左も分かってないがきだ
Why do you think
何のために監視官と執行官の区分けがあると思う
we have the classifications
of Inspectors and Enforcers?
It's in order to avoid the risk of
having healthy people's Psycho-Pass
健常な人間が犯罪捜査でサイコパスを曇らせるリスクを回避するためだ
get clouded by criminal investigations.
二度と社会に復帰できない潜在犯を身代わりに立てているからこそ
We use latent criminals, who can
never return to society, in our place.
That's precisely why you can fulfill
your duty while protecting your mind!
君は自分の心を守りながら職務を遂行できるんだ
That's not teamwork!
そんなのチームワークじゃありません
Solving crimes or protecting
our own Psycho-Pass...
犯罪を解決するのと 自分のサイコパスを守るのと
Which on earth is more important?!
いったいどっちが大切なんですか
Do you wanna throw away your career?
君はキャリアを棒に振りたいのか？
Are you going to sacrifice
everything you've built so far?
ここまで積み上げてきたもの全てを犠牲にするつもりか？
私は…
It's...
It's certainly true that I'm new.
私は確かに新人です
And you are a respectable
senior to me, Inspector Ginoza.
宜野座監視官は尊敬すべき先輩です
But please don't forget that we're
on equal footing in terms of our rank!
しかし　階級上はまったくの同格ということを忘れないでください
I'm managing my Hue just fine.
自分の色相はちゃんと管理できています
You may be senior to me,
but I'd like you to restrain yourself from
いくら先輩とはいえ　職場で執行官たちの目の前で
questioning my ability at the
workplace and in front of the Enforcers!
私の能力に疑問符をつけるような発言は慎んでいただきたい
I can't believe he...
あんな言い方…
Where are you going?
どこに行くんだい
I'm going to file a protest
with the bureau chief.
局長を通して抗議します
Any chance of you passing on that, missy?
やめておいてくれないかな お嬢ちゃん
But...
でも
宜野座監視官はな 父親が潜在犯なんだ
Inspector Ginoza's father is a latent criminal.
What?
えっ
He was a child when the Sibyl System
had just been put into operation.
あいつの子供時代ってのは まだシビュラ判定が実用化されて間もないころでな
Terrible misunderstandings
and rumors about latent criminals
世間では潜在犯に対する過剰な誤解やデマが横行していた
were common in those days.
If a family member happened
to show a high Crime Coefficient,
親兄弟から犯罪係数が計測されたというだけでその家族までもが
that alone caused the rest of the family
to be treated as if they were the same.
同類の扱いを受けた
I'm sure he suffered quite a bit.
さぞやつらい思いをしたことだろうさ
When a detective gets deeply
involved in an investigation, in the end
刑事が捜査に深くのめり込めば結局は
the Sibyl System starts keeping an
eye on them just like it does the criminals.
シビュラシステムから犯罪者の同類としてマークされるようになる
Committing a crime
or cracking down on crimes...
犯す側も取り締まる側も
Both sides face the same phenomenon
called crime. There's no difference.
同じ犯罪という現象に直面していることに違いはない
Now there are Enforcers,
but before they created that position,
今みたいに執行官なんて役職ができる前には
there were many detectives who
were diagnosed as latent criminals like that.
そうやって潜在犯と診断された刑事が大勢いた
Inspector Ginoza's father was one of them.
宜野座監視官の父親もその一人だ
I didn't know...
そうだったんですか…
That's why he can't forgive
those who run a risk on their own.
だからあいつは 自ら進んで危険を冒すやつを許せない
And yet, Kogami,
his former colleague, was also...
なのに　同僚だった狡噛も…
Yes, I know.
ええ　知ってます
He feels he was betrayed twice.
First by his father and then by his colleague.
父親と　相棒に
二度も　裏切られたという思いがあるんだ
That's why he acts like that towards you.
だから　お嬢ちゃんに対する態度もあんなふうになっちまう
But even so...
でも　だからって…
間違っちゃいないさ
You're right.
Missy, you do have a family
and friends too, don't you?
お嬢ちゃん　あんたにだって家族や友達がいるんだろ？
If your Psycho-Pass gets clouded,
あんたのサイコパスが曇ったら
this time, those people will suffer
the same hardships Nobuchika did.
今度はその人たちが伸元と同じ苦しみを背負うことになる
In order to avoid that,
we, Enforcers, are here.
そうならないために俺たち執行官がいる
Do you think Mr. Kogami
thinks that way, too?
狡噛さんもそんなふうに思ってるんでしょうか？
He used to.
以前はな
だが　今は…
But now...
...he might be oblivious to everything
that's not related to that Makishima guy.
例のマキシマってやつのこと以外
目に入らなくなっちまってるのかもしれん
I won't capture him alive.
私は生け捕りにしないよ
Is that really okay?
いいのか？
Of course. Why would
you capture him alive?
もちろん
どうして生け捕りなんて？
It seems that you haven't
noticed it yourself, so I'll tell you this.
君は気付いていないようだから言っておくが
Shinya Kogami...
When you speak that name,
狡噛慎也
その名前を　口にするとき
you look quite amused.
君はとても楽しそうなんだよ
I'll give you your justice
Before you destroy and get destroyed
Pay karma's price, and let's go together
Monster without a name
御伽話（フェアリーテイル）は
童话般的美好
Looks like the fairy tale died a moment ago
さっき死んだみたい
在刚刚已经死去
In a hospital ward made of bricks,
I found it hard to sing
煉瓦の病棟で
瓦墙下的病房
うまく歌えなくて
在这里我无法歌唱
霧に煙る夜
灰灰蒙蒙的夜
Red moon, come out on this foggy night
浮かべ赤い月
悬浮飘红的月
ほらみて　私を
快 看我
Now look at me, don't avert your gaze
目を逸らさないで
别移开你的视线
I was born behind black iron bars
黒い鉄格子の中で
黑黑的铁栅背后
私は生まれてきたんだ
我来到这个世界
Wish for payback for the evil done
悪意の代償を願え
祈祷恶的代价
望むがままにお前に
如你所愿给你吧
As you wish, I'll give you your justice
さあ与えよう正義を
给与你
Before you destroy and get destroyed
壊して　壊される前に
破坏掉正义 在自身毁灭之前
Pay karma's price, and let's go together
因果の代償を払い
付出因果的代价
共に行こう
一起走吧
Monster without a name
名前のない怪物
无名怪兽
A world where humans' state of mind and the tendency of their
personalities can be quantified. While all sorts of inclinations
are recorded and policed, these measured numbers
used to judge people's souls are commonly called "Psycho-Pass."
This story is fiction.
The names of all individuals and organizations that appear in the show
are fictitious and have no relation to those in existence in the real world.